♪You are a devil.♪
♪But you are my medicine.♪
Hello.
Are you at home?
We've been neighbors for so long,
this is my first time visiting your house.
Ah.
Wow,
I don't even have this photo.
You were so young back then.
Yeah.
This telescope can really see my house.
It's quite clear.
Maybe I should put one up at my place too.
Then I can see you.
It's only fair, right?
Is that why you're here?
Yeah.
Have you had breakfast yet?
Huh?
The noodles you made for me last time were really good.
This time, let me cook for you.
Have a try.
Have you made up your mind?
Yes.
Some things
must be put to an end.
Can you really face her?
After all, she's your mom.
I used to
live in the world she created for me,
thinking power and status,
being the Lin family's heir was everything.
But when I met you,
and learned the truth, I realized
how ridiculous my life had been.
Don't you hate me?
I dragged you into this mess.
I did hate you,
for showing up,
for exposing the truth,
for making me lose everything.
But now,
I'm grateful to you.
You made me see myself clearly.
Xintian,
I'm not doing this for you,
I'm doing it for myself.
I'll take her to turn herself in.
As for our issues,
we'll deal with them after this is all over.
But now,
we're on the same side,
right?
Yeah.
The noodles are getting cold.
Eat up.
Lawyer Guan,
I'm the police officer in charge of Su Wei's case.
Su Wei had a sudden allergic shock yesterday.
After emergency treatment,
she is now out of danger.
She asked me to tell you that
She will cooperate in exposing those involved.
After our investigation,
the allergenic drug
was smeared on the clothes brought by the family in advance.
The family also confirmed that
Clothes came from a self-proclaimed friend of hers.
It's all been cleaned up.
All the necessary
connections have been made.
But the police is very strict.
If Su Wei speaks, we...
What a bunch of losers!
You can't even handle this.
Go to Xu Tianyou.
We need to hide for a while.
He knows what to do.
Mr. Lin,
you're back.
Still calling me Mr. Lin?
In my heart,
you'll always be Mr. Lin.
Really?
Then in your heart,
what am I to you?
I...
I'm your driver.
A driver?
Ah,
or
my biological father?
Do you know how many people you've harmed?
Do you know how many bad things you've done?
Killing Wang Jiming,
harming Gu Qingyu,
and now trying to kill Guan Tiantian.
Your hands are just as bloody
as hers.
I didn't mean to.
I was forced to do it.
She promised me
you would have a good life.
You would be the heir to the Lin Group.
I...
I did it for your sake.
So you sold me out.
You traded your son's life
for your stable position as the driver, right?
No.
It's not like that, Jiming.
I...
I'm sorry.
I have no choice.
She...
She controls everything.
I...
I don't even have the courage to acknowledge you.
What's the point of saying this now?
Jiming.
Poisoning your husband,
stealing his identity,
and murdering your stepson.
Wen Shiyi,
how can you deny this?
Where did you get
all these forged documents?
What do you want?
You want to accuse your mother
with these?
You're not my mother.
You're the devil.
If I'm not your mother,
who raised you
for the past thirty years?
Who taught you to walk and talk?
Who
stayed up all night
when you were sick?
Who
gave you the best education,
and made you the Lin heir?
If I'm not your mother,
then who am I?
Ah.
What you say today is useless.
I will take you to turn yourself in.